SA CompatPack "Story" Outline

Pre-E1M1: 
  Flora is doing a shopping "trip"/tour on Earth, and happens to find a strange tablet amongst the shops, unbeknowestedly one of the same the SA-protagonist had used to try to find a way to resurrect his son David a few centuries ago, somehow having been dug up from the lake he had thrown them into during the E4 ending of the original SA. Sending some interest from this tablet, she buys it for a fairly low price, all things considered.
  Taking the tablet with her to her hotel room, she falls asleep for the night, but then awakens in what appears to be a different place, a recreation of the house the SA protagonist lived in, and was used to travel to the many eldritch 'dreamlands' featured in SA's original incarnation, essentially throwing Flora into a "retreading" of the SA protagonists steps, but also being subtly guided by various eldritch forces trying to use her now to bring them to material plane as she travels the worlds.
  
Post-E1M4:

Post-E1M8:

Post-E2M4:

Post-E2M8:

Post-E3M4:

Post-E3M8:

Post-E4M4:

Post-E4M8:

Post-E5M4:

Post-E5M8:

